<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>conference on Erin Robinson</title>
    <link>https://erinrobinson.info/categories/conference/</link>
    <description>Recent content in conference on Erin Robinson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 09:20:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://erinrobinson.info/categories/conference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Open Project Design</title>
      <link>https://erinrobinson.info/talk/agu-open-project-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 09:20:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erinrobinson.info/talk/agu-open-project-design/</guid>
      <description>Julie Lowndes and I presented an invited paper “Open Project Design: Lessons from the NASA Openscapes Framework” virtually at the 2021 American Geophysical Union (AGU) annual conference, in a session “Open Science In Action” convened by Dr. Chelle Gentemann and colleagues.
Abstract: Open source software is about more than code: it’s about welcoming a broadening audience to a shared vision and planning for sustainability. We’ll cover considerations for open project design focused on inclusion, community building, web presence, and technology choices, sharing strategies from the NASA Openscapes Framework as an example.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invited - Putting Data to Work</title>
      <link>https://erinrobinson.info/talk/leptoukh-lecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 18:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erinrobinson.info/talk/leptoukh-lecture/</guid>
      <description>Abstract     We live in a world rich with data, where use and reuse would benefit not just science but also serve national security and society-at-large. Air quality impacts from forest fires, which are increasing in frequency, is one example of large, data-intensive science with societal impacts. Understanding long-range transport of smoke where I started my career and worked with Dr. Greg Leptoukh, for whom this lecture is named, required a variety of datasets from satellite, surface observations and models.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
